<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Historyxsl.xsl"?>
<Mars_bookshop>
		<book>
			<Genre>History</Genre>
			<title>The Sacred History</title>
			<author>
				<FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
				<LastName>Booth</LastName>
			</author>
			<published_date>29 January 2013</published_date>
			<price>60</price>
			
			<image>
			https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81tmGkwUwLL._SL1500_.jpg
            </image>
			<description>
				The Sacred History is an account of the workings of the supernatural in history. It tells the epic story of angels, from Creation,
				to Evolution through to the operations of the supernatural in the modern world.
				This tale of how people and peoples have been helped by angels and other angelic beings is woven into a spellbinding narrative that brings together Krishna, Moses, Buddha, Elijah, Mary and Jesus, Mohammed, 
				Joan of Arc, the angels who helped Hungarian Jews persecuted by the Nazis, and stories from African, Native American and Celtic traditions
			</description>
		</book>
		<book>
			<Genre>History</Genre>
			<title>The Wright Brothers</title>
			<author>
				<FirstName>David</FirstName>
				<LastName>David McCullough</LastName>
			</author>
			<published_date>August 2015</published_date>
			<price>50</price>
			
			<image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/515EjXI21kL.jpg</image>
			<description>
				On December 17, 1903, at Kitty Hawk, North Carolina, Wilbur and Orville Wright's Wright Flyer became the first powered, heavier-than-air machine to achieve controlled, 
				sustained flight with a pilot aboard. The Age of Flight had begun. 
				How did they do it? And why? David McCullough tells the extraordinary and truly American story of the two brothers who changed the world.
			</description>
		</book>
		<book>
			<Genre>History</Genre>
			<title>The Forgotten Village</title>
			<author>
				<FirstName>Lorna</FirstName>
				<LastName>Cook</LastName>
			</author>
			<published_date>1818</published_date>
			<price>40</price>
			
			<image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/51vd4z1zXeL.jpg</image>
			<description>
				1943: the world is at war, and the villagers of Tyneham are being asked to make one more sacrifice: 
				to give their homes over to the British army. But on the eve of their departure, a terrible act will cause three of them to disappear forever.
			</description>
		</book>
		<book>
			<Genre>History</Genre>
			<title>My Husbands Secrets</title>
			<author>
				<FirstName>Louise</FirstName>
				<LastName>Sharland</LastName>
			</author>
			<published_date>2022</published_date>
			<price>87</price>
			
			<image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/51RgVTY3vdL.jpg</image>
			<description>
				Grief-stricken, Ali can’t bring herself to believe that her beloved Matthew is gone.
				The smell of his aftershave lingers in their bedroom. His voice still rings out on their answerphone. She sees his face in the eyes of strangers.
				But as the months pass, and her family and friends rally round, Ali starts to uncover secrets that Matthew kept from her.
			</description>
		</book>
		<book>
			<Genre>History</Genre>
			<title>The Secret History of The World </title>
			<author>
				<FirstName>Mark</FirstName>
				<LastName>Booth</LastName>
			</author>
			<published_date>23 February 2015</published_date>
			<price>60</price>
			<image>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91MuAnB2LPL._SL1500_.jpg</image>
			<description>
				They say that history is written by the victors. 
				But what if history—or what we have come to know as history—has been written by the wrong people? What if everything we’ve been told is only part of the story?

			</description>
		</book>
</Mars_bookshop>
